A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Cruger, George, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Cultural Development Commission - House Bill 862, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Cultural Development Study Commission, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- D: General, 1934-1942 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- D: General, 1949-1955 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- D: General, 1949-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 42)
- D: General, 1954-1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- D: General, 1958-1972, folder 1 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- D: General, 1958-1972, folder 2 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- D: General, 1958-1972, folder 3 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- D: General, 1958-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 43)
- D: General, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Dance Society: Sub-Committee Meeting 1957 Nov 11 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Dance Conference 1971 Feb 20, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Daniel, John H., 1961-1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Daniel, Mrs. Robert W., 1959-1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Darden, Governor, 1942-1944 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Davenport, Carson, 1935-1944 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Davenport, Carson, 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 44)
- Davis, Hester, 1949-1955 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1935-1944 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 45)
- Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1945-1955 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1945-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 46)
- Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Day, Elizabeth Nottingham, 1934-1945 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Day, Elizabeth Nottingham, 1934-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 47)
- Day, Horace, 1954-1959 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Day, Mr. and Mrs. Horace, 1945-1954 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Day, Mr. and Mrs. Horace, 1945-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 48)
- Dearstyne, Howard, 1950-1957 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- DeJarnette, Edmund T., 1954-1966 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- de la Warr, Earl, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- deMare, Marie, 1949-1957 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- deMare, Marie, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- DeNatalie, Richard, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Department and Division Head Reports, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Design for Christmas [1], 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Design for Christmas [2], 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Design for the Theatre, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Design in Scandinavia [1], 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Design in Scandinavia [2], 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Design in Scandinavia [3], 1953-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Design in Scandinavia [3], 1953-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Design in Scandinavia 1954 Jan 15-Feb 14, 1953-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Design in Scandinavia 1954 Jan 15-Feb 14, 1953-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Design in Scandinavia 1954 Jan 15 - Feb 14, 1953-1954 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Design in Scandinavia: American Tour, 1951-1954, folder 1 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Design in Scandinavia: American Tour, 1951-1954, folder 2 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Design in Scandinavia: American Tour, 1951-1954, folder 3 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Design in Scandinavia: American Tour, 1951-1954 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Design in Scandinavia: Commercial Sales, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Design in Scandinavia: Committees, 1952-1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Design in Scandinavia: Compliments, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Design in Scandinavia: Memo of 2 June 1952 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Design in Scandinavia: Memo of 6 March 1953 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Design in Scandinavia: New York Times Article, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Design in Scandinavia: Opening, 1953-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Design in Scandinavia: Opening, 1953-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Design in Scandinavia: Program 1953-1954, 1952-1955 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Design in Scandinavia: Responses to Invitations, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Design in Scandinavia: Scandinavian and General Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 1 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Design in Scandinavia: Scandinavian and General Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 2 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Design in Scandinavia: Scandinavian and General Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 3 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Design in Scandinavia: Scandinavian and General Correspondence, 1951-1954, folder 4 of 4 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Designer, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Designer Craftsmen USA, 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Designer Craftsmen USA, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Detroit Museum of the Arts, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Development Committee: Meeting 1957 November 26 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Development Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Dioramas, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Director's Overseas Travel, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Discovery Cruise to "Land of Maya" 1973 March 17-31, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Division Head Memos, 1946-1973, folder 1 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Division Head Memos, 1946-1973, folder 2 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Division Head Memos, 1946-1973, folder 3 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Division Head Memos, 1946-1973 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 49)
- Division Head Memos, 1969-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Division Head Memos, 1969-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Division Head Memos, 1969-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 50)
- Doctors' Wives Luncheon, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Dohn, Helen, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Donations and Gifts, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Donations and Gifts, 1974-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 51)
- Donations to the Museum, 1964-1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Donations to the Museum, 1964-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 52)
- Donations, Contributions, Gifts, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Donations, Contributions, Gifts, 1971-1973 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 53)
- Donations, Contributions, Gifts, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Donations, Contributions, Gifts, etc., 1973-1974 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 54)
- Donors (Plaques), 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Double-Decker Bus, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Double-Decker Bus, 1961-1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Dunston, Mr. and Mrs. Bruce, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- duPont, Mrs. Alfred I., 1935-1945 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- duPont, Mrs. Alfred I., 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- duPont, Mrs. Alfred I., 1958-1968 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- duPont, Mrs. Alfred I., 1958-1968 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 55)
- Dyas, James 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- E: General, 1934-1938 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- E: General, 1945-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- E: General, 1945-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 56)
- E: General, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Eastern Oncology Study Group Special Reception, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Economic Resource Task Force (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Educational Programs: Museum Methods Program (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Educational Programs: Summer of 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Educational Programs: Three Days in April Student Workshop, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Educational Programs: Two Days in November Workshop, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Egyptian Art, 1951-1954 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Egyptian Art, 1955-1960 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Egyptian Art, 1955-1960 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Egyptian Art, 1955-1960 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Egyptian Gallery Opening 1961 April 14, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Egyptian Gallery Opening 1961 April 14, 1961 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 57)
- Employment Issues and Travel Plans, 1956-1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- England 1607 1957 May 17 - September 1, 1954-1957, folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- England 1607 1957 May 17 - September 1, 1954-1957, folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- English Decorative Arts Gallery Opening, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Entertainment: Previews, Parties, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Entertainment Committee, 1944-1950, folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Entertainment Committee, 1944-1950, folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Entertainment Committee, 1950-1954, folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Entertainment Committee, 1950-1954, folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Entertainment Committee, 1950-1956 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Entertainment Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Entertainment Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Entertainment Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Entertainment CommitteeL Meeting, 1957 October 21 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Evans, Mrs. Arthur Kelly, 1950-1951 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Evening of Fashion, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Evening Programs, 1950-1952 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Events, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Events: American Federation of Arts (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Events: Artmobile IV 1966, April 6, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Events: Barton, Mr. and Mrs. - Party, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Events: Behind-the-Scenes Tours, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Events: Butzner Dinner, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Events: Christmas Party, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Events: Christmas Preparations 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Events: College Drama Festival, 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Events: Council Lecture - Luncheon, 1962-1965 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Events: DeJarnette Luncheon, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Events: Fashion Gala, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Events: Film Preview - "Museum in Action", 1961 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Events: Garden Club of Virginia, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Events: Governor Harrison Reception 1962 January 16, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Events: Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Events: Grand Reopening 1963 September 27, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Events: Indrani Dancers - Party 1961 October 6, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Events: Jenkins, Alfred Peyton - Party, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- Events: Junior League Luncheon, 1961-1967 (Box 90, Folder 20)
- Events: Law, Common Law, Justice and Lawyer 1959 May 17, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Events: Lurcat, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Events: Lurcat, 1970 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Events: Members' Dinner 1960 November 25, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Events: Members' Dinner 1960 October 29, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Events: Mielziner, Jo, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Events: National Art-Collections Fund 1964 Visit, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Events: National Art-Collections Fund Visit, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Events: National Conference of Editorial Writers 1960, 1958-1960 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Events: National Conference of Editorial Writers 1960, 1958-1960 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 58)
- Events: National Secretaries Association Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Events: National Trust for Historic Preservation 1972 November 3, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Events: New Member Reception 1969 October 24, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Events: New Member Reception 1970 November 13, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Events: New Member Reception 1971 April 16, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Events: Nicholas and Alexandria 1972 May 3, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Events: Norfolk Preview and Reception 1962 January 16, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Events: Parsons Fashion Show 1967 May 8, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Events: Parsons Fashion Show 1967 May 8, 1966-1971 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Events: Patrons Gala 1970 February 13, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Events: Patrons Preview, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Events: President's Reception for New Members, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Events: Preview Evening VMTAS (Theatre), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Events: Refreshments - College Presidents, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Events: Richmond Bar Association 1970 May 27, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Events: Richmond Bar Association Dinner 1972 January 27, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Events: Richmond Little Symphony, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Events: Richmond Rotary Club, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Events: Robinson House Opening 1964, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Events: Smith College Club Dinner, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Events: Thank You Parties, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Events: The Hospitality and Information Service (THIS) (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Events: Three Days in March, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Events: Tobacco Festival Hostesses, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Events: Trustee Dinner, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Events: Trustee Dinner, 1957 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 22)
- Events: Tuckahoe Garden Club Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- Events: United Daughters of the Confederacy Tea, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Events: Vedder, Elihu, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Events: Viennese Ball - Council, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Events: Virginia Architects/Planners 1972 October 10, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Events: Virginia Artists Jury 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Events: Virginia Artists Jury 1959, 1958-1959 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 59)
- Events: Virginia Artists Lecture 1959, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Events: Virginia Interior Designers 1973 March 16, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Events in the Museum: General, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Executive Committee: General, 1944-1947 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Executive Committee: General, 1944-1947 (RESTRICTED) (Box 27, Folder 60)
- Executive Committee: General, 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Executive Committee: General, 1949-1952 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Executive Committee: General, 1949-1952 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 61)
- Executive Committee: General, 1950-1953 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Executive Committee: General, 1950-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 62)
- Executive Committee: General, 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Executive Committee: General, 1953-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 63)
- Executive Committee: General, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Executive Committee: General, 1954-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 64)
- Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [1] (Box 27, Folder 57)
- Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [1] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 65)
- Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [2] (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [2] (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 66)
- Executive Committee: General, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- Executive Committee: General, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 67)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1948-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 68)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1950-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 69)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1953-1955 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1953-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 70)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 71)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 January 9 (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 January 9 (RESTRICTED) (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 February 12 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 February 12 (RESTRICTED) (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 March 19 (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 March 19 (RESTRICTED) (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 May 10 (Box 90, Folder 28)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 September 9 (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 November 22 (Box 90, Folder 30)
- Executive Committee: Minutes, 1957 November 22 (RESTRICTED) (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Executive Committee: Pending, 1951-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee: Pending, 1951-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 76, Folder 72)
- Executive Luncheons, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Exhibition Schedule, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Exhibitions, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Exhibitions, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Exhibitions, 1973-1974 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Exhibitions, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Exhibitions, 1974 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Exhibitions, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Exhibitions: 20th Century Engineering, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Exhibitions: 25th Anniversary Exhibition, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Exhibitions: 25th Anniversary - Treasures of America, 1958-1961 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Exhibitions: 25th Anniversary - Treasures of America, 1958-1961 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Exhibitions: Albers, Joseph and Annie, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Exhibitions: Aldrich Catalog, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Exhibitions: American Painting 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Exhibitions: American Painting 1966, 1962-1966 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Exhibitions: American Painting 1970 - Protest, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Exhibitions: American Sculpture, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Exhibitions: Architects, Designers and Photographers, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Exhibitions: Architects, Designers and Photographers 1966, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Exhibitions: Art Nouveau, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Exhibitions: Bache Collection 1966 January 28 - February 28, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Exhibitions: Barlach, Ernst 1963 October 4-20, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Exhibitions: Bicentennial, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Exhibitions: Blake, William - Poet, Printer, Prophet 1965 November 15 - December 26, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Exhibitions: Block Collection 1967 January 13 - February 12, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Exhibitions: Borrowed and Bought 1960 December 16, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Exhibitions: Chinese Loan Exhibition, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Exhibitions: Civil War Centennial 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Exhibitions: Collector of the Year - Clement E. Conger, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Exhibitions: Collector of the Year 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Exhibitions: Collector of the Year 1973, 1972-1973 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Exhibitions: Contemporary French Tapestries / Lurcat, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Exhibitions: Contemporary Glass, 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Exhibitions: Contemporary Glass, 1958-1960 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Exhibitions: Coptic Exhibition and Lecture 1959 May 1, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Exhibitions: Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Exhibitions: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Exhibitions: Davies, Arthur B., 1963 January 11- February 10, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Exhibitions: Davies, Arthur B., 1963 January 11 - February 10, 1962-1963 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Exhibitions: Design in Finland 1965 April 2 - May 2, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Exhibitions: Egyptian Exhibition, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Exhibitions: Egyptian Scribe, 1965 April 2 - May 2, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Exhibitions: Egyptian Scribe, 1965 April 2 - May 2, 1964-1965 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Exhibitions: Egyptian Scribe, 1965 April 2 - May 2, 1964-1965 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 17-20)
- Exhibitions: Florence and Tuscany, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Exhibitions: Formgivers at Mid-Century and Lecture, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Exhibitions: Formgivers at Mid-Century and Lecture, 1959-1960 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Exhibitions: Formgivers at Mid-Century and Lecture, 1959-1960 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Exhibitions: Forms from Israel and Lecture, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Exhibitions: Garbish Collection, American Primitive Paintings, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Exhibitions: Greatest Story Ever Told, 1962-1965 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Exhibitions: Greatest Story Ever Told, 1962-1965 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Exhibitions: Greek Gold (Treasures from Alexander), 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Exhibitions: Greek Gold (Treasures from Alexander), 1963-1966 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Exhibitions: Greek Gold (Treasures from Alexander), 1963-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Exhibitions: Greek Gold - Russian Loan, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Exhibitions: Greek Line, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Exhibitions: Gund Collection of Western Art Preview, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Exhibitions: Gund Collection of Western Art Preview, 1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Exhibitions: Heeramaneck Collection, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Exhibitions: Hogarth, William, 1967 January 30 - March 5, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Exhibitions: Hollywood, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Exhibitions: Homer, Winslow, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Exhibitions: Homer, Winslow, 1963-1964 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Exhibitions: Hopper, Edward, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Exhibitions: In Virginia, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Exhibitions: In Virginia, 1970-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Exhibitions: India in Virginia 1969 February 3 - March 9, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Exhibitions: L'Oiseau qui n'existe pas, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Exhibitions: Landscape Architecture Today, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Exhibitions: Lewis Collection (Art Museum of Corpus Christi), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Exhibitions: Master Drawings from Cooper Union and Lecture, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Exhibitions: Masterpieces of American Silver, 1956-1960 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Exhibitions: Masterpieces of Oriental Art, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Exhibitions: McMullan Rugs, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Collection of British Painting, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Collection of British Painting, 1961-1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Collection - Basil Taylor Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Collection - Basil Taylor Correspondence, 1961-1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Collection - Basil Taylor Correspondence (Duplicate Copies), 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition, 1962-1963 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition - Catalogue, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition - Invitations, Programs, etc., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition - John Baskett, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Exhibitions: Mellon Exhibition - Mr. Mellon's Speech, Printing Job, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Exhibitions: Michelangelo, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Exhibitions: Modern Mosaics, 1954-1961 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Exhibitions: Moore, Henry, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Exhibitions: Moore, Henry, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Exhibitions: Neutra, Richard J. Display 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Exhibitions: Old Master Painting 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Exhibitions: Old Master Painting 1972, 1971-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Exhibitions: Once Invisible, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Exhibitions: Photography as an Art, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Exhibitions: Possibilities for Museum, 1948-1953, folder 1 of 3 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Exhibitions: Possibilities for Museum, 1948-1953, folder 2 of 3 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Exhibitions: Possibilities for Museum, 1948-1953, folder 3 of 3 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Exhibitions: Possible Traveling Exhibitions, 1947-1949 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Exhibitions: Possible Traveling Exhibitions, 1948-1952 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Exhibitions: Possible Traveling Exhibitions, 1948-1952 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Exhibitions: Pre-Hispanic Gold, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Exhibitions: Price, Vincent, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Exhibitions: Primitive African Exhibition, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Exhibitions: Print Exhibition - Today's Prints, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Exhibitions: Printing for Commerce, 1950-1951 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Exhibitions: Programs - Possible Exhibitions, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Exhibitions: Randolph-Macon Women's College Collection, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Exhibitions: Resident Craftsmen - Joe Monk, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)